http://www.santafeworkshops.com/about/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form, or subscribe to our online communications.When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To improve our web siteWe continually strive to improve our web site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, is used for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, with the sole exception of our educational partners. To send periodic email The email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an orderWe offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.
DO WE USE COOKIES?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?
On infrequent occasions we share our list of names and mailing addresses with our educational partners who wish to share information and special offers about photographic products with you. We will share only your name and mailing address for a one time use. We may share information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our web site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our web site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
CHILDRENS ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our web site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on June 23, 2010
CONTACTING US
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Santa Fe Photographic WorkshopsPO Box 9916Santa Fe, New Mexico 87504(505) 983-1400 www.santafeworkshops.com
View Workshop Calendar (34 upcoming workshops)
